

#### CONTACT

- +549-1131822452
- ✓ damitepl@gmail.com
- Nuñez, CABA, Argentina
- www.linkedin.com/in/dteplitz

#### **EDUCATION**

2020 - Present UTN

Software Engeneering

11/2022 - 12/2022 UDEMY

• AWS certified developer

#### **SKILLS**

- Java
- SQL
- SpringBoot
- Kafka
- JUnit
- Hibernate
- AWS
- MongoDB
- Angular
- Docker
- Gradle
- Maven
- Jenkins

# LANGUAGES

- English (Fluent)
- Spanish (Native)

# DAMIAN TEPLITZ

### SOFTWARE ENGINEER

#### **PROFILE**

I am a highly motivated developer with passion for coding and continuous learning. I balance my strong technical skills with effective collaboration and clear communication. I am dedicated to writing clean, maintainable code, always prioritizing both the user experience and client needs to deliver robust, user-friendly solutions.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Monnet Payment Solutions**

6/2023 - PRESENT

Full Stack Developer

- Led design and development projects for payment processing and our own backoffice.
- Improved code performance through refactoring.
- Provided project estimations.
- Ensured project continuity and collaborated with cross-functional teams to deliver user-centric and client-focused solutions.
- Using Java 17, Springboot, Maven, JUnit, MySQL, MongoDB, AngularJS, AWS, JPA, Kafka, Jenkins and Jira.

#### Prisma medios de pago

2/2022 - 5/2023

Java Software Developer

- Worked with cutting-edge technologies to build a new payment processing platform.
- Collaborated with an excellent team to deliver robust, scalable solutions.
- Contributed to the product's successful production launch.
- Using Java 17, SpringBoot, jPos, JUnit dBeaber, AWS, GitLab, Gradle, Kotlin, Hibernate, Opensearch and Jira.

#### Finnegans

06/2019 - 01/2022

08/2018 - 06/2019

Full Stack Developer

- Delivered personalized solutions for major clients, enhancing system functionality and user experience.
- Collaborated closely with clients to understand their needs, ensuring tailored and effective implementations.
- Successfully reduced system downtime by implementing optimized code and efficient database queries.
- Using Java 11, SpringBoot, Maven, Eclipse, SQL, JavaScript, AWS, Jira

# Menhir

Full Stack Developer

- Developed web applications using Java, PHP, JQuery, Javascript, CSS, HTML, SQL, Bootstrap.
- · Adapted quickly to new technologies
- Collaborated effectively in a team, and focused on delivering clientoriented solutions, ensuring code quality and maintainability.